GIA GIAMPINO

INFO

ADDRESS

1007 Eagles Ridge Rd, Brewster, NY, 10509, United States

PHONE

845-490-5469

giagiampino@gmail.com

SKILLS

Microsoft Office Suite

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$

Google Suite

Adobe Illustrator

• • 0 0 0

Code Writing

• • 0 0 0

Relationship Management

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$

Office Administration

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$

Digital Communication

Customer Relations

....

Product Promotion

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$

Data Entry

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$

Data Visualization

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$

Social Media

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$

PROFILE

Recent college graduate (May 2019) Majoring in Journalism and Design/Data Visualization, combined with experience in social media, marketing, and design communications. Exploring career opportunities in creative leadership where my education, skills and experience can be used to achieve business growth objectives.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Digital Media Management, Amie Smith Realty

North Salem, NY

Aug 2018 - Present

Focused on market penetration and product awareness to drive sales.

Front Desk Administrator, Keller Williams Realty **Partners**

Northern Westchester,

May 2018 - Sept 2018

Performed administrative functions including Excel spreadsheets, emails, correspondence, appointment scheduling, copying, and faxes

Social Media Director. The Cardillo Real Estate Network

Yorktown Heights, NY

Mar 2018 - May 2018

Aligned all social media strategies with targeted demographics. Used various social media platforms. Coordinated meetings, maintained web pages, and served as a liaison to clients.

Personal Assistant, Stevers Inc.

Somers, NY

Jan 2019 - Jan 2019

Worked as a Personal Assistant to a CEO.

EDUCATION

Parsons School of Design, BA in Journalism + Design/Data Visualization

New York, NY

Aug 2015 - May 2019

GPA: 3.8/4.0

Rutgers Business School

Newark, NJ

Jan 2017 - May 2017

New York City College of Technology

New York, NY

Aug 2015 - Aug 2016

Sep 2011 - Jun 2015

REFERENCES

Mrs. Melissa Riley from Keller Williams Realty Partners, Northern Westchester

melissabrownriley@gmail.com | 203-253-9222

Mr. Louis Cardillo from The Cardillo Real Estate Team cardillo@kw.com | 914-481-2223

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Member: National Society for Leadership and Success, Sigma Alpha Pi

Showcase Member: Congressional Art Competition